Guide to the Latino Studies Program Records, 1978-1993
Latino Studies Program Records, 1978-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Latino Studies Program records,
53-19-2695
Cornell University. Latino Studies Program.
2 cubic ft.
Subject files
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Administrative and historical records of the Program; also subject files, and records of the Revelations/Revalcions Art Show (Novemebr 6 - December 19, 1993).
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Latino Studies Program was formerly the Hispanic American Studies Program.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Administrative and historical records of the Latino Studies Program; also subject files, and records of the Revelations/Revalcions Art Show (November 6 - December 19, 1993).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Latino Studies Program.; Cornell University. Hispanic American Studies Program.
Subjects:
Hispanic American college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Hispanic Americans--Study and teaching.; Hispanic Americans--Societies, clubs, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- LaMujer Newsletters, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Texas Observer Newspapers, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hispanic Arts Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cuban American National Council, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- National Hispanic Scholarship Fund, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- La Frontera Nesletters, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minority Education at Cornell - Part I and II, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- National Directory of Putero Rican Professionals in Higher Education in the U.S., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- List of Hispanic Associations, not dated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Encuentro Newsletters, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hispanics in SW Texas. Demographic and School enrollment trends, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- English Plus Project, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Grant applications, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vernon Briggs - HASP, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- HASP events, Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Advertising for HASP, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- HASP 3 year budget estimates, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Latino student's suggestions on making it through medical school, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- National Clearinghouse for Bilingual Education Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Other universities - Hispanic Studies Programs, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- National Puerto Rican Coalition Newsletters and Information, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- National Hispanic University/California - information, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Puerto Rican Studies Program, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Native American Studies Proposal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Center for Research on Women Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Hispanic Elderly, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hispanic Women's Center, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Youth Opportunities Unlimited, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cornell - programs - fellowships, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Programming, Fall 1987, Sp. 1988, Sp. 1989; Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Course listings-HASP, Fall 1989, Sp. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Hurrican Hugo, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Puerto Rico - At a Political Crossroad Conference/ print info, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34-36)
- Puerto Rico - Conference publicity, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Puerto Rico - Endowment for the Humanities, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- An American Festival, Sept. 17-27, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Seminar Series - Planning, Fall 1987; Fall 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- HASP Conference - Draft/Papers, March 10, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- HASP Symposium, October 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- HASP Symposium - Conference, October 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chavez, Linda - U.S. English - President, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Ronald Gonzales - Correspondence and Art Work, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Maria Brito - Writings and Announcements, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Celia Alvarez - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Rimer Cardillo - Writings and Art Work, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Amalia Mesa-Bains - Correspondence and Publications, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Daniel Martinez - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Daniel Martinez - Announcements and Arts Works, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Daniel Martinez - Resume and Writings, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Gronk - Correspondence and Publications, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Day of the Dead, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Revlelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Book Trials, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Raphael Montanez Ortiz - Resume and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Edin Velez - Documentary Premiere Latino Month 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Edin Velez - Online Production, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Sylvia Morales - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Documentary Latino Month, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Critics Symposium, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Contracts, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Edin Velez - Filmmaker Appointments, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Video Documentary Information, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Catalogue Sales, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Filmmaking Online/Offline Documentary, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Mailing List, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Ondine Chauoya - Resume, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Jennifer Gonzales - Resume, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Press Information, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Cornell Tradition Newsletters, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Risk Mangagement Forms, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Publication Services, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Johnson Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Site Visit - Raphael Montanez Ortiz and Edin Velez, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Materials List, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Artists' Information Packets, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Revelations/Revelaciones Art Show - Publicity, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Year of the Hispanic Performance, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Hispanic Arts Festival, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Portfolio - Jose Piedra Fall Arts Festival, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)